[Music]
at long last things are set in stone
we're signing papers in the next coming
weeks to officially purchase our home
at the end of this video i share some
images of the interior and renovation
progress i'm very relieved that we do
seem like we finally have a floor with
much more coming soon
as some of you may know we're trying to
renovate an older barn in the forest on
my fiancee's parents former property
it will be an interesting change to no
longer be surrounded by open fields
leaving the more arid hills and prairies
to something very different
it will be lovely to live among so many
trees i always give them names and
attach personalities to them
it might sound strange but i do look
forward to making friends with the pines
you will meet them soon enough
[Music]
um
so
[Music]
due to getting a little seasonal cold i
did not get much done this week but i
appreciate you coming along anyway
i was working on this lino cut today and
a memory just came to mind which i
thought was quite funny um i got an
email from someone several days ago
that told me that they had looked at my
shop
and they enjoyed my art but they were
wondering why all my
fairies looked so sad
what i have in mind when i'm painting
them is that if i am traipsing about in
the wilderness in a enchanted meadow or
by babbling brook or a somehow enchanted
grove
i
feel that if i came across them by
accident looking through the leaves of
grass
that they would actually be rather
curious or introspective or
thoughtfully gazing back at me unsure as
to what to make of this strange little
human staring at them i just love the
idea that they would be quite concerned
about my presence and perhaps a little
curious
and also wondering whether or not i'm a
fairy friend so yes so there you go that
is why my fairies are not always smiling
gleefully they are more demure and more
gentle in their expressions and the
reason for that is because i have a very
very very strange mind i am a strange
little lady so i also think as well
probably a little bit of my own
personality is projected onto it because
i
smile when i'm around people but when
i'm by myself or especially out in
nature i'm usually not very self-aware
at all i can be quite serious and a lot
of what is happening is through
my other senses through my eyes and my
ears i'm listening and looking with such
intensity around me and around at all
the beauty that i do often forget what
the expression on my face is
so the other thing i got up to this week
was that i went and i inspected the
house that we are going to purchase it
does seem like everything is
pretty much
set in stone at this point so it's very
very exciting but i went to go see it
and went to go see the renovations that
are happening and it was very exciting i
have noticed that online on youtube it
seems very popular for people to share
how they renovate a home
and i wanted to tell you guys that
unfortunately i'm not going to share
that part because
i'm not taking any part in it
my fiance and his father both have
worked in construction for much of their
lives and they're very educated on how
to do it and i definitely would be
more of a burden than help if i tried to
insert myself in that situation so
i've been watching from the sidelines
and cheering on
aware that i'm absolutely terrified of
power tools and
i really couldn't do much of anything in
regards to working on a house so we do
have a floor though so that's really
great
we didn't have that for quite a bit so
it is very exciting
and
yeah i did however put quite a bit of
emphasis on
being able to find some things to
decorate the house because i do love to
paint and decorate as you guys can tell
it is definitely a passion of mine and i
really like to do it on a budget as well
that is very important to me to try to
diy anything i possibly can or find
secondhand items or thrifted items it's
about a two to three hour drive to get
to the nearest city and it was very
exciting to go visit i really don't get
out that much i don't think i travel
almost at all anymore only to see family
and it was just a blast i got to see all
these antique shops and second-hand
shops and try to look for furniture to
purchase
if i am able to
it was funny because i initially went to
the city specifically looking for
a couch
and then i went into a new furniture
store and i saw that the couches were
thousands of dollars and i just walked
out of there almost immediately then i
went to a antique shop and a secondhand
shop i still couldn't find anything i
decided that i would just upholster an
old couch that luke was going to get rid
of so my abuela is visiting from puerto
rico she's very good at upholstering
furniture so she's going to help me
upholster the couch which is really
exciting so i'm very excited to
introduce her and have you meet her so
that being said i appreciate you guys
understanding this week was a little bit
different and i really wasn't able to do
as much as i usually do and i will see
you very soon i'm sending you all my
love and i hope you have a wonderful day
take care of yourselves and i will see
you very very soon goodbye
[Music]
so
you